Letterpress Copybooks of Samuel Gompers and William Green, Presidents on Microfilm 5431 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Letterpress Copybooks of Samuel Gompers and William Green, Presidents on Microfilm
1908-1925
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Federation of Labor (AFL)
Gompers, Samuel
Green, William
5431 mf
38.11 cubic feet
343 microfilm reels
Records (documents), microfilm.
Microfilm of letterpress copybooks of AFL presidents Samuel Gompers and William Green.
5650544
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 15, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 12, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The American Federation of Labor (AFL) was the first federation of labor unions in the United States. It was founded in May of 1886 in Columbus, Ohio. Samuel Gompers of the Cigar Makers' International Union was elected president every year except one up until he passed away in 1924. The AFL was the largest union grouping in the United States in the first half of the 20th Century, even after the Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) was formed.
In 1955 the AFL merged with the CIO (longtime rival), to form the AFL-CIO, a federation of unions which remains today.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence relating to the establishment of the Federation and Gompers early involvement with American and international socialism and his eventual disenchantment with the American movement. Documentation of particular strikes to be found in the separate collection: AFL Records - Pt. 1 & 2. Strikes and Agreement Files, 1893-1953
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5402 mf: Correspondence of American Federation of Labor President William Green on Microfilm 5760 mf: American Federation of Labor Records, Part 2 on Microfilm 5761 mf: William Green Papers on Microfilm
Labor leaders -- United States.; Gompers, Samuel, 1850-1924; Green, William, 1872-1952; American Federation of Labor.
5650544
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 1-2 - 9/21/1883-1888 (Reel 1-2)
  Scope and Contents
  positive
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 3 - 9/12/1888-7/9/1889, 1888-1889 (Reel 3)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 4 - 7/19/1889-8/7/1890, 1889-1890 (Reel 4)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 5 - 8/7/1890-6/30/1891, 1890-1891 (Reel 5)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 6 - 6/30/1891-2/2/1892, 1891-1892 (Reel 6)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 7-8 - 2/3/1892-3/20/1893, 1892-1893 (Reel 7-8)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 9-10 - 3/21/1893-4/21/1894, 1893-1894 (Reel 9-10)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 11-12 - 4/23/1894-11/4/1895, 1894-1895 (Reel 11-12)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 13-15 - 2/28/1895-7/29/1896, 1895-1896 (Reel 13-15)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 16-17 - 7/29/1896-2/5/1897, 1896-1897 (Reel 16-17)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 18-19 - 2/5/1897-5/18/1897 (Reel 18-19)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 20 - 5/19/1897-8/24/1897 (Reel 20)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 21 - 8/25/1897-11/19/1897 (Reel 21)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 22 - 11/19/1897-3/15/1898, 1897-1898 (Reel 22)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 23 - 3/15/1898-6/20/1898 (Reel 23)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 24 - 10/7/1898-1/21/1899 (Reel 24)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 25 - 10/7/1898-1/21/1899, 1898-1899 (Reel 25)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 26-27 - 1/21/1899-4/11/1899 (Reel 26-27)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 28 - 4/13/1899-7/22/1899 (Reel 28)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 29 - 7/22/1899-9/26/1899 (Reel 29)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 30 - 9/26/1899-12/1/1899 (Reel 30)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 31-32 - 11/27/99 - 3/14/99, 1899; 1 (Reel 31-32)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 31-32 - 11/27/1899-3/14/1/899, 2 (Reel 31-32)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 33 - 3/14/1900-5/5/1900 (Reel 33)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 34-35 - 5/7/1900-6/7/1900 (Reel 34-35)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 36 - 7/13/1900-9/5/1900 (Reel 36)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 37 - 9/6/1900-10/26/1900 (Reel 37)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 38-39 - 10/27/1900-12/11/1900 (Reel 38-39)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 40 - 1/2/1901-2/18/1901 (Reel 40)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 41 - 2/18/1901-4/4/1901 (Reel 41)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 42 - 4/4/1901-5/10/1901 (Reel 42)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 43 - 5/10/1901-6/18/1901, 1 (Reel 43)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 44 - 6/18/1901-7/12/1901, 2 (Reel 43)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 44 - 6/18/1901-7/12/1901 (Reel 44)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 45 - 7/12/1901-8/27/1901 (Reel 45)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 46 - 8/28/1901-10/15/1901 (Reel 46)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 47 - 10/15/1901-11/12/1901 (Reel 47)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 48 - 11/12/1901-12/16/1901 (Reel 48)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 49 - 12/2/1901-12/31/1901 (Reel 49)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 50 - 1/2/1902-1/24/1902 (Reel 50)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 51 - 1/24/1902-2/15/1902 (Reel 51)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 52 - 2/15/1902-3/11/1902 (Reel 52)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 53 - 3/11/1902-4/3/1902 (Reel 53)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 54 - 3/31/1902-4/26/1902 (Reel 54)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 55 - 4/28/1902-5/22/1902 (Reel 55)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 56 - 5/22/1902-6/14/1902 (Reel 56)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 57 - 6/14/1902-7/10/1902 (Reel 57)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 58 - 7/10/1902-8/21/1902 (Reel 58)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 59 - 8/21/1902-9/23/1902 (Reel 59)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 60 - 9/23/1902-10/18/1902 (Reel 60)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 61 - 10/20/1902-11/24/1902 (Reel 61)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 62 - 11/11/1902-12/13/1902 (Reel 62)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 63 - 12/15/1902-12/31/1902 (Reel 63)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 64 - 1/2/1903-1/22/1903 (Reel 64)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 65 - 1/22/1903-2/10/1903 (Reel 65)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 66 - 2/11/1903-2/28/1903 (Reel 66)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 67 - 3/2/1903-3/16/1903 (Reel 67)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 68 - 3/17/1903-4/1/1903 (Reel 68)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 69 - 4/1/1903-4/16/1903 (Reel 69)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 70 - 4/16/1903-4/22/1903 (Reel 70)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 71 - 4/22/1903-5/16/1903 (Reel 71)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 72 - 5/15/1903-6/2/1903 (Reel 72)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 73 - 6/2/1903-6/20/1903 (Reel 73)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 74 - 6/22/1903-7/16/2903 (Reel 74)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 75 - 7/16/1903-8/6/2903 (Reel 75)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 76 - 8/3/1903-8/22/1903 (Reel 76)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 77 - 8/22/1903-9/12/1903 (Reel 77)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 78 - 9/12/1903-10/5/1903 (Reel 78)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 79 - 10/5/1903-10/27/1903 (Reel 79)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 80 - 10/27/1903-11/24/1903 (Reel 80)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 81 - 11/7/1903-12/12/1903 (Reel 81)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 82 - 12/11/1903-1/4/1904 (Reel 82)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 83 - 1/2/1904-1/19/1904 (Reel 83)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 84 - 1/19/1904-2/5/1904 (Reel 84)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 85 - 2/5/1904-3/1/1904 (Reel 85)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 86 - 3/1/1904-4/2/1904 (Reel 86)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 87 - 4/2/1904-5/2/1904 (Reel 87)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 88 - 5/2/1904-5/24/1904 (Reel 88)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 89 - 5/24/1904-6/15/1904 (Reel 89)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 90 - 6/15/1904-7/15/1904 (Reel 90)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 91 - 7/15/1904-8/16/1904 (Reel 91)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 92 - 8/16/1904-9/20/1904 (Reel 92)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 93 - 9/20/1904-10/22/1904 (Reel 93)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 94 - 10/22/1904-12/22/1904 (Reel 94)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 95 - 12/22/1904-1/17/1905 (Reel 95)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 96 - 1/17/1905-2/8/1905 (Reel 96)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 97 - 2/8/1905-3/7/1905 (Reel 97)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 98 - 3/6/1905-4/3/1905 (Reel 98)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 99 - 4/3/1905-4/26/1905 (Reel 99)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 100 - 4/26/1905-5/26/1905 (Reel 100)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 101 - 5/20/1905-7/6/1905 (Reel 101)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 102 - 7/6/1905-8/14/1905 (Reel 102)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 103 - 8/14/1905-9/16/1905 (Reel 103)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 104 - 9/18/1905-10/21/1905 (Reel 104)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 105 - 10/28/1905-12/15/1905 (Reel 105)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 106 - 12/15/1905-1/10/1906, 1905-1906 (Reel 106)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 107 - 1/10/1906-2/9/1906 (Reel 107)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 108 - 2/9/1906-3/10/1906 (Reel 108)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 109 - 3/10/1906-4/4/1906 (Reel 109)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 110 - 4/4/1906-4/30/1906 (Reel 110)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 111 - 4/30/1906-5/28/1906 (Reel 111)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 112 - 5/28/1906-6/27/1906 (Reel 112)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 113 - 6/27/1905-8/1/1906, 1905-1906 (Reel 113)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 114 - 7/31/1906-8/24/1906 (Reel 114)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 115 - 8/23/1906-10/5/1906 (Reel 115)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 116 - 10/5/1906-10/27/1906 (Reel 116)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 117 - 10/27/1906-12/18/1906 (Reel 117)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 118 - 12/18/1906-1/10/1907, 1906-1907 (Reel 118)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 119 - 1/10/1907-2/5/1907 (Reel 119)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 120 - 2/5/1907-2/26/1907 (Reel 120)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 121 - 2/26/1907-3/20/1907 (Reel 121)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 122 - 3/20/1907-4/12/1907 (Reel 122)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 123 - 4/12/1907-5/10/1907 (Reel 123)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 124 - 5/10/1907-6/12/1907 (Reel 124)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 125 - 6/12/1907-7/11/1907 (Reel 125)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 126 - 7/11/1907-8/20/1907 (Reel 126)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 127 - 8/27/1907-9/21/1907 (Reel 127)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 128 - 9/21/1907-10/16/1907 (Reel 128)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 129 - 10/16/1907-12/2/1907 (Reel 129)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 130 - 12/2/1907-12/28/1907 (Reel 130)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 131 - 12/28/1907-1/21/1908, 1907-1908 (Reel 131)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 132 - 1/20/1908-2/17/1908 (Reel 132)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 133 - 2/17/1908-3/11/1908 (Reel 133)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 134 - 3/11/1908-4/3/1908 (Reel 134)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 135 - 4/3/1908-4/30/1908 (Reel 135)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 136 - 4/30/1908-5/29/1908 (Reel 136)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 137 - 5/28/1908-7/2/1908 (Reel 137)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 138 - 7/2/1908-8/6/1908 (Reel 138)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 139 - 8/5/1908-9/2/1908 (Reel 139)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 140 - 9/1/1908-9/3/1908 (Reel 140)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 141 - 9/29/1908-10/29/1908 (Reel 141)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 142 - 10/22/1908-12/9/1908 (Reel 142)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 143 - 12/9/1908-1/7/1909, 1908-1909 (Reel 143)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 144 - 1/8/1909-2/10/1909 (Reel 144)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 145 - 2/10/1909-3/9/1909 (Reel 145)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 146 - 3/8/1909-4/1/1909 (Reel 146)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 147 - 4/1/1909-5/6/1909 (Reel 147)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 148 - 5/5/1909-6/5/1909 (Reel 148)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 149 - 6/5/1909-8/6/1909 (Reel 149)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 150 - 8/6/1909-11/24/1909 (Reel 150)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 151 - 11/9/1909-12/22/1909 (Reel 151)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 152 - 12/13/1909-2/1/1910, 1909-1910 (Reel 152)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 153 - 2/1/1910-2/24/1910 (Reel 153)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 154 - 2/24/1910-3/24/1910 (Reel 154)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 155 - 3/25/1910-4/23/1910 (Reel 155)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 156 - 4/25/1910-5/24/1910 (Reel 156)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 157 - 5/24/1910-7/6/1910 (Reel 157)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 158 - 7/6/1910-7/30/1910 (Reel 158)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 159 - 7/30/1910-8/30/1910 (Reel 159)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 160 - 8/30/1910-9/28/1910 (Reel 160)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 161 - 9/28/1910-10/26/1910 (Reel 161)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 162 - 10/26/1910-11/14/1910 (Reel 162)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 163 - 11/14/1910-12/24/1910 (Reel 163)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 164 - 12/14/1910-1/28/1911, 1910-1911 (Reel 164)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 165 - 1/30/1911-2/27/1911 (Reel 165)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 166 - 2/27/1911-3/25/1911 (Reel 166)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 167 - 3/25/1911-4/30/1911 (Reel 167)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 168 - 4/20/1911-5/27/1911 (Reel 168)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 169 - 5/27/1911-7/7/1911 (Reel 169)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 170 - 7/7/1911-8/14/1911 (Reel 170)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 171 - 8/14/1911-10/9/1911 (Reel 171)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 172 - 10/9/1911-12/8/1911 (Reel 172)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 173 - 12/6/1911-1/11/1912, 1911-1912 (Reel 173)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 174 - 1/12/1912-2/14/1912 (Reel 174)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 175 - 2/13/1912-3/15/1912 (Reel 175)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 176 - 3/15/1912-4/12/12 (Reel 176)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 177 - 4/12/1912/5/18/1912 (Reel 177)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 178 - 5/17/1912-7/8/1912 (Reel 178)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 179 - 7/9/1912-8/16/1912 (Reel 179)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 180 - 8/17/1912-9/30/1912 (Reel 180)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 181 - 9/30/1912-12/2/1912 (Reel 181)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 182 - 12/3/1912-1/16/1913, 1912-1913 (Reel 182)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 183 - 1/16/1913-2/14/1913 (Reel 183)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 184 - 2/13/1913-3/21/1913 (Reel 184)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 185 - 3/21/1913-4/28/193 (Reel 185)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 186 - 4/28/1913-7/9/1913 (Reel 186)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 187 - 7/8 1913-9/24/1913 (Reel 187)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 188 - 9/25/1913-11/23/1913 (Reel 188)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 189 - 11/22/1913-1/10/1914, 1913-1914 (Reel 189)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 190 - 1/10/1914-2/10/1914 (Reel 190)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 191 - 2/9/1914-3/2/1914 (Reel 191)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 192 - 2/27/1914-4/10/1914 (Reel 192)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 193 - 4/10/1914-5/9/1914 (Reel 193)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 194 - 5/9/1914-6/10/1914 (Reel 194)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 195 - 6/10/1914-7/8/1914 (Reel 195)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 196 - 7/8/1914-8/6/1914 (Reel 196)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 197 - 8/6/1914-9/8/1914 (Reel 197)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 198 - 9/2/1914-10/12/1914 (Reel 198)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 199 - 10/10/1914-11/30/1914 (Reel 199)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 200 - 11/30/1914-12/31/1914 (Reel 200)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 201 - 12/31/1914-1/18/1915, 1914-1915 (Reel 201)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 202 - 1/28/1915-2/16/1915 (Reel 202)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 203 - 2/13/1915-3/18/1915 (Reel 203)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 204 - 3/8/1915-4/10/1915 (Reel 204)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 205 - 4/12/1915-5/18/1915 (Reel 205)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 206 - 5/14/1915-6/17/1915 (Reel 206)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 207 - 6/16/1915-7/7/1915 (Reel 207)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 208 - 7/7/1915-8/14/1915 (Reel 208)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 209 - 8/13/1915-9/13/1915 (Reel 209)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 210 - 9/8/1915-10/4/1915 (Reel 210)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 211 - 9/30/1915-10/29/1915 (Reel 211)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 212 - 10/29/1915-12/24/1915 (Reel 212)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 213 - 12/22/1915-1/11/1916, 1915-1916 (Reel 213)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 214 - 1/11/1916-2/5/1916 (Reel 214)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 215 - 2/4/1916-2/29/1916 (Reel 215)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 216 - 2/29/1916-3/26/1916 (Reel 216)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 217 - 3/17/1916-4/7/1916 (Reel 217)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 218 - 4/7/1916-4/22/1916 (Reel 218)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 219 - 4/21/1916-5/15/1916 (Reel 219)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 220 - 5/15/1916-6/2/1916 (Reel 220)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 221 - 6/7/1916-7/10/1916 (Reel 221)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 222 - 7/10/1916-8/1/1916 (Reel 222)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 223 - 8/2/1916-8/24/1916 (Reel 223)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 224 - 8/24/1916-9/19/1916 (Reel 224)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 225 - 9/19/1916-10/13/1916 (Reel 225)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 226 - 10/13/1916-11/10/1916 (Reel 226)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 227 - 11/10/1916-12/161/1916 (Reel 227)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 228 - 12/16/1916-1/13/1917, 1916-1917 (Reel 228)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books. 1883-1924 - Wm. Green Letter books 1925: vol. 229 - 1/15/1917-2/6/1917 (Reel 229)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 230 - 2/3/1917-3/1/1917 (Reel 230)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 231 - 3/1/1917-3/27/1917 (Reel 231)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 232 - 3/26/1917-4/25/1917 (Reel 232)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 233 - 4/25/1917-5/22/1917 (Reel 233)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 234 - 5/22/1917-6/13/1917 (Reel 234)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 235 - 6/18/1917-7/14/1917 (Reel 235)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 236 - 7/14/1917-8/8/1917 (Reel 236)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 237 - 8/7/1917-8/3/1917 (Reel 237)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 238 - 7/31/1917-10/5/1917 (Reel 238)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 239 - 10/3/1917-10/22/1917 (Reel 239)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 240 - 10/27/1917-12/12/1917 (Reel 240)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 241 - 12/5/1917-1/12/1918, 1917-1918 (Reel 241)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 242 - 1/3/1918-1/30/1918 (Reel 242)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 243 - 1/30/1918-2/26/1918 (Reel 243)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 244 - 2/26/1918-3/22/1918 (Reel 244)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 245 - 3/16/1918-4/13/1918 (Reel 245)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 246 - 4/11/1918-5/10/1918 (Reel 246)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 247 - 5/10/1918-6/17/1918 (Reel 247)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 248 - 6/18/1918-8/17/1918 (Reel 248)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 249 - 7/17/1918-8/20/1918 (Reel 249)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 250 - 8/15/1918-10/2/1918 (Reel 250)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 251 - not available (Reel 251)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 252 - 12/9/1918-1/18/1919, 1918-1919 (Reel 252)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 253 - 1/9/1919-3/19/1919 (Reel 253)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 254 - 3/13/1919-5/22/1919 (Reel 254)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 255 - 5/20/1919-7/18/1919 (Reel 255)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 256 - 7/11/1919-8/21/1919 (Reel 256)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 257 - 8/21/1919-9/20/1919 (Reel 257)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 258 - 9/19/1919-10/21/1919 (Reel 258)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 251 - 10/21/1919-11/20/1919 (Reel 259)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 260 - 11/18/1919-12/20/1919 (Reel 260)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 261 - 12/19/1919-1/20/1920 (Reel 261)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 262 - 1/27/1920-2/21/1920 (Reel 262)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 263 - 2/24/1920-3/18/1920 (Reel 263)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 264 - 3/19/1920-3/23/1920 (Reel 264)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 265 - 3/24/1920-4/13/1920 (Reel 265)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 266 - 4/12/1920-5/17/1920 (Reel 266)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 267 - 5/15/1920-6/29/1920 (Reel 267)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 268 - 6/29/1920-7/28/1920 (Reel 268)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 269 - 7/29/1920-8/28/1920 (Reel 269)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 270 - 8/19/1920-9/28/1920 (Reel 270)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 271 - 9/29/1920-10/31/1920 (Reel 271)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 272 - 10/30/1920-12/6/1920 (Reel 272)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 273 - 12/6/1920-1/4/1921, 1920-1921 (Reel 273)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 274 - 1/4/1921-2/1/1921 (Reel 274)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 275 - 2/1/1921-3/4/1921 (Reel 275)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 276 - 3/4/1921-3/24/1921 (Reel 276)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 277 - 3/28/1921-4/18/1921 (Reel 277)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 278 - 4/19/1921-5/21/1921 (Reel 278)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 279 -5/21/1921-7/11/1921 (Reel 279)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 280 - 7/11/1921-7/27/1921 (Reel 280)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 281 - 7/27/1921-8/19/1921 (Reel 281)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 282 - 8/20/1921-9/17/1921 (Reel 282)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 283 - 9/16/1921-10/4/1921 (Reel 283)
- Samuel Gompers Letter books vol. 284 - 10/4/1921-10/26/1921 (Reel 284)